<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on The Whiterocker</title>
    <link>https://mendoza-git.github.io/the-whiterocker/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on The Whiterocker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 15:01:35 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mendoza-git.github.io/the-whiterocker/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Whiterocker Clubhouse</title>
      <link>https://mendoza-git.github.io/the-whiterocker/projects/lounge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mendoza-git.github.io/the-whiterocker/projects/lounge/</guid>
      <description>Photo provided by The Whiterocker The Clubhouse All members have 24 hour access to the clubhouse. Only registrered or temporary club members have access to the lounge area.
To inquire about access, contact memberships@thewhiterocker.com.
For private event requests, contact management@thewhiterocker.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Whiterocker | Poker</title>
      <link>https://mendoza-git.github.io/the-whiterocker/projects/poker/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mendoza-git.github.io/the-whiterocker/projects/poker/</guid>
      <description>Photo provided by The Whiterocker Poker at The Whiterocker The club provides all members with free access to a collection of game tables designed for card games. Equipment for various game variations will also be provided for free by the club. Games are always free to play with the exception of private rentals. We recommend members contact The Whiterocker management to see if the equipment is availible.
Private Rentals Club members have the ability to rent the designated a game table provided by the club for a maximum time of 8 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Whiterocker | Café</title>
      <link>https://mendoza-git.github.io/the-whiterocker/projects/cafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mendoza-git.github.io/the-whiterocker/projects/cafe/</guid>
      <description>Cool Water / Davidoff #10. Cool Water Davidoff Cool Water has secured its place among the top 10 best men&amp;rsquo;s fragrances for going to the gym for several compelling reasons. The fragrance&amp;rsquo;s fresh and aquatic notes, including mint and lavender, create an invigorating and revitalizing aura that aligns well with the active and energetic atmosphere of a gym. Cool Water&amp;rsquo;s light and clean scent profile ensures that it is not overpowering, providing a subtle and refreshing fragrance that won&amp;rsquo;t distract or overwhelm others in the gym environment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
